<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- Logging in -->
    <string name="help_item_1_1_title">Login</string>
    <string name="help_item_1_1_image">help_normal_login</string>
    <string name="help_item_1_1_text">
        Enter your Babybuddy Server URL, username, and password. Then press login to connect
        the Babybuddy App to the Babybuddy Server.
    </string>

    <string name="help_item_1_2_title">Insecure Login</string>
    <string name="help_item_1_2_image">help_insecure_http_warning</string>
    <string name="help_item_1_2_text">
        If you use an http-address instead of an https-address, the application will show you this warning. Only use this feature for local BabyBuddy
        servers in a network that you control!
    </string>

    <!-- Create/manage Timers  -->
    <string name="help_item_2_1_title">Default Timers</string>
    <string name="help_item_2_1_image">help_create_default_timers</string>
    <string name="help_item_2_1_text">
        After logging in, the first thing you should do is setup the timers that you want to use.
        Typically, you can click "Create Default Timers" to create timers for some primary activities
        you might want to log.
    </string>

    <string name="help_item_2_2_title">Timer Setup</string>
    <string name="help_item_2_2_image">help_timer_setup</string>
    <string name="help_item_2_2_text">
        If you started the app while timers were already running in your Baby Buddy app, this button
        is not available. Instead, the pre-existing timers will appear on screen.
        You can overwrite the current timers and (re-)create the default timers via the
        "Recreate Default Timers" option from the menu.
    </string>

    <string name="help_item_2_3_title">Configuring Timers</string>
    <string name="help_item_2_3_image">help_timers_configure2</string>
    <string name="help_item_2_3_text">
        Alternatively, you can assign the timers to a (different) activity by using the drop-down menu.
    </string>

    <!-- Overview -->
    <string name="help_item_3_1_title">Overview</string>
    <string name="help_item_3_1_image">help_overview</string>
    <string name="help_item_3_1_text">
        After logging in, you find buttons for logging activities in the upper part of the screen
        and a history of recently logged activities in the lower part of the screen.
        If you log activities for multiple children, you can swipe horizontally to switch between children.
    </string>


    <!-- Using Timers -->
    <string name="help_item_4_1_title">Using Timers</string>
    <string name="help_item_4_1_image">help_play_button_highlight</string>
    <string name="help_item_4_1_text">
        Press the "play"-button to start a timer for the listed activity.
    </string>

    <string name="help_item_4_2_title">Using Timers</string>
    <string name="help_item_4_2_image">help_notes_button_highlight</string>
    <string name="help_item_4_2_text">
        While the timer is running, you can add notes by pressing the "notes" buttons.
    </string>

    <string name="help_item_4_3_title">Using Timers</string>
    <string name="help_item_4_3_image">help_save_button_highlight</string>
    <string name="help_item_4_3_text">
        To stop the timer and store the activity, press the "save" button.
    </string>

    <string name="help_item_4_4_title">Feedings</string>
    <string name="help_item_4_4_image">help_feeding_form</string>
    <string name="help_item_4_4_text">
        Saving a feeding will trigger a second form, where the feeding type (e.g., solid food) and
        method must be entered before the feeding can be stored.
    </string>

    <!-- Logging Diapers -->
    <string name="help_item_5_1_title">Logging Diapers</string>
    <string name="help_item_5_1_image">help_save_diaper_highlight</string>
    <string name="help_item_5_1_text">
        The top controls allow logging of diaper changes. Select the type of diaper and press the
        "save" button to log the activity. You can optionally add notes.
    </string>

    <!-- Event history -->
    <string name="help_item_6_1_title">Event history</string>
    <string name="help_item_6_1_image">help_events</string>
    <string name="help_item_6_1_text">
        The history at the bottom of the screen shows the most recent activities of
        the selected child. You can edit entries by pressing the entry in the history for three
        seconds. This will open the corresponding page in the BabyBuddy app.
        To delete an entry, press the red "delete" button.
    </string>
</resources>