<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- Logging in -->
    <string name="help_item_1_1_title">Login</string>
    <string name="help_item_1_1_image">help_normal_login</string>
    <string name="help_item_1_1_text">
        Enter your Babybuddy Server URL, username, and password. The press login to connect
        the Babybuddy App to the Babybuddy Server.
    </string>

    <string name="help_item_1_2_title">Insecure Login</string>
    <string name="help_item_1_2_image">help_insecure_http</string>
    <string name="help_item_1_2_text">
        If you use a http-address instead of a https-address,…
    </string>

    <string name="help_item_1_3_title">Insecure Login</string>
    <string name="help_item_1_3_image">help_insecure_http_warning</string>
    <string name="help_item_1_3_text">
        … the application will show you this warning. Only use this feature for local BabyBuddy
        servers in a network that you control!
    </string>

    <!-- Create/manage Timers  -->
    <string name="help_item_2_1_title">Timer Setup</string>
    <string name="help_item_2_1_image">help_timer_setup</string>
    <string name="help_item_2_1_text">
        After you logged in, the first thing you should do is setup the timers. Depending how you
        use babybuddy, there might be some timers already preconfigured when using the app for the
        first time or not…
    </string>

    <string name="help_item_2_2_title">Default Timers</string>
    <string name="help_item_2_2_image">help_create_default_timers</string>
    <string name="help_item_2_2_text">
        If no timers are defined yet, you can click on the "Create Default Timers" button to create
        a set of default timers for the primary baby buddy activities you might want to log.
    </string>

    <string name="help_item_2_3_title">Default Timers</string>
    <string name="help_item_2_3_image">help_create_default_timers_menu</string>
    <string name="help_item_2_3_text">
        If timers are already defined, you can create the same set of timers by selecting the
        "Recreate Default Timers" option from the menu
    </string>

    <string name="help_item_2_4_title">Configuring Timers</string>
    <string name="help_item_2_4_image">none</string>
    <string name="help_item_2_4_text">
        Alternatively, you can configure the activity for pre-existing timers to match reuse them
        directly.
    </string>

    <!-- Overview -->
    <string name="help_item_3_1_title">Overview</string>
    <string name="help_item_3_1_image">none</string>
    <string name="help_item_3_1_text">
        After logging in, the application will show a full-screen overview for a given child. If
        you have multiple children, you can swipe horizontally to change the view to another child.
    </string>

    <string name="help_item_3_2_title">Overview</string>
    <string name="help_item_3_2_image">none</string>
    <string name="help_item_3_2_text">
        The upper part of the application shows buttons for logging activities for the current
        child. The lower part lists logged events for that child in reverse chronological order.
    </string>

    <!-- Logging Diapers -->
    <string name="help_item_4_1_title">Logging Diapers</string>
    <string name="help_item_4_1_image">none</string>
    <string name="help_item_4_1_text">
        The top controls allow logging of diaper changes. Click the wet or solid button to check the
        type, then…
    </string>

    <string name="help_item_4_2_title">Logging Diapers</string>
    <string name="help_item_4_2_image">none</string>
    <string name="help_item_4_2_text">
        … optionally, add a notes-text and finally press the save button to save the diaper change.
    </string>

    <!-- Using Timers -->
    <string name="help_item_5_1_title">Using Timers</string>
    <string name="help_item_5_1_image">none</string>
    <string name="help_item_5_1_text">
        Press the "play"-button to start a timer for any of the listed activity types.
    </string>

    <string name="help_item_5_2_title">Using Timers</string>
    <string name="help_item_5_2_image">none</string>
    <string name="help_item_5_2_text">
        While the timer is running you can add notes as usual.
    </string>

    <string name="help_item_5_3_title">Using Timers</string>
    <string name="help_item_5_3_image">none</string>
    <string name="help_item_5_3_text">
        When the timer should be logged, you press the save button to store the activity.
    </string>

    <string name="help_item_5_4_title">Feedings</string>
    <string name="help_item_5_4_image">none</string>
    <string name="help_item_5_4_text">
        Feeding timers will show a special form after storing. The feeding type and feeding method
        need to be entered before a feeding can be stored.
    </string>

    <!-- Event history -->
    <string name="help_item_6_1_title">Event history</string>
    <string name="help_item_6_1_image">none</string>
    <string name="help_item_6_1_text">
        The lower portion of the application shows a list of the most recent logged activities of
        a given child. You can delete individual entries by pressing the red delete button next to
        the actvity. In addition, you can long-press an entry to open the corresponding page for the
        logged activity in the BabyBuddy app directly.
    </string>
</resources>